P. Issac Samarpan Raju

Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh padalaissacsamarpanraju2_zxt@indeedemail.com +91-9704878345

I have more than 10 years working experience in Social Development sector in project management positions. 2 years of working experience in software testing, and around 3 years working experience as facility in computer applications .

Work Experience

Network project coordinator cum manager HR and administration

Tribal Educational Rural Development Society (TERDS) - Araku, Andhra Pradesh April 2010 to Present

The organization is working among the tribal communities present in Vishakhapatnam Agency areas. The organization is based at Araku, Visakhapatnam district. TERDS is also convening a State level NGOs Network working among Primitive Tribal Group (PTG) for overall development of PTG's namely Andhra Pradesh Adama Adivasi Initiative (AAADI) (PTG) Network. There are 8 partners in this network all are PTG heeded organization present in 6 districts of Andhra Pradesh. The network is working on overall development of Primitive Tribal Groups (PTG) in AP.

- # Overall administration of project to meet its objective.
- # Preparation of action plane and Coordinating the Network activities as per in the project
- # Managing the projects and activities (planning and executing) of organization
- # Responsible for implement HR policy of organization
- # Documentation (Preparation of reports, Processes documentation, Correspondence with donors etc)

Coordinator data analysis

Gamana - Visakhapatnam, Andhra Pradesh February 2008 to March 2010

Gamana is a NonGovernmental Organization, based in Hyderabad. The organization is working in nine districts of Andhra Pradesh on different environmental and health-based projects. I was working in Visakhapatnam the project on which we are working is water and sanitation. The organization advocates with Government official to provide safe drinking water to the people of our working area by the implementation of Solid Waste Management Rules. involved in study on wast management by farmacompanies and their effect on enveronment

- ✓ Managing the project
- ✓ System Maintenance
- ✓ Documentation
- ✓ Water quality testing

Software test engineer

SSR INFOCOM SOLUTIONS - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh January 2006 to February 2008

SSR infocomm was a softwere development organization. Web and client server based products were produced. My role in this organization was quality control engineer.

- ✓ Analysis of the functional and business requirements documents
- ✓ Designing the test cases according to the specification
- ✓ Executing test cases to ensure that product meet the specification.
- ✓ Preparing and reporting the bug reports

Faculty Member

Mcc Academy - Malkangiri, Chhattisgarh 2003 to 2006

Teaching languages (C, C++)

Teaching Scripts (JavaScript)

Teaching data base concepts (SQL Server, Dbase and foxpro)

Teaching basic of computers (Operating systems application MS-Word, MS XI, Powrpoint etc.

System distraction

Education

PGDCA

DIT institute vishakapatnum

B.Sc. in Physics

Berhampur University - Brahmapur, Orissa

Skills / IT Skills

- Project Administration (7 years)
- Software Testing (2 years)
- Software Training (3 years)

Awards / Achievements

First class Distinction

May 2000

I have award first class in Physics honours and distinction in B.Sc. degree from Berhampur university in the year 2000

.

Additional Information

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages & scripts C, C++, Visual Basic 6.0, Java script Operating Systems MS Dos, Windows Family, Linux/Unix Database Oracle 8i, MS Access, FoxPro, SQL Server 2005 Packages MS-Office. (MS-Word, MS-xI, MS-PowerPoint) Automation Testing Tools QTP 9.0